Loretta J. Ross Papers, 1956-2005
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IV. ORGANIZATION FILES
  - American Civil Liberties Union 1989-90, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - American Friends Service Committee (Box 6)
  - Affirmative Action Program 1987-90 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - "Call for a National Consultation on the Crisis in the African American Community" 1989-90 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - National Disarmament Program 1989, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Nationwide Women's Program (Box 6)
  - Listen Real Loud 1986-90 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Meetings, memos and correspondence 1987-90 (Box 6, Folder 11-13)
  - "Women Poverty and Economic Power" 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Peace Education Program 1987-89, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Third World Coalition 1990, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous printed material 1977-91 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - American Indian Women Against Domestic Violence - American Society for Training and Development Minority Network 1984, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Americans for Indian Opportunity 1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Amnesty International 1988-89 (Box 7, Folder 7-8)
  - Anarchist Black Cross - Association of Black Women's Historians 1980-93 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Association of Community Organizations for Reform Now - Black Health Research 11Foundation 1986-91, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Black Women Organized for Political Action - Black Women Together 1985-88 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Black Women's Agenda 1987-88 (Box 7, Folder 12-13)
  - Black Women's History Project - Black Women's Symposium Planning Committee 1985-88 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - B'Nai B'rith Women - Boston Women's Health Book Collective 1984-89 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - California Abortion Rights League-Catholics For Free Choice 1984-93, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights - Center for Reproductive Law and Policy 1987-91, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Center for Democratic Renewal
    - Board of Directors 1991, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Clippings 1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence
      - External 1992-94 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Internal 1991-92, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Employment/personnel 1990-92 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Expenses and financial material 1991-93 (Box 9, Folder 1-4)
    - Georgia Project undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Grant proposals undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Mailing lists undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Notes 1993-94, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Publications
      - Activist Update 1995 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - The Monitor 1990-95 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous 1987-93, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Subjects, [see also SERIES VI. SUBJECTS]
      - Hate crimes (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Ku Klux Klan 1985, undated, [see also Georgia Project] (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Militia movement 1995; Oklahoma City bombing, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - South Africa 1993-94 (Box 10, Folder 5-8)
      - South Africa 1993-94 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Documents from South Africa 1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Yearly reviews 1992-94 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Women's Watch 1993 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Center for Global Education
    - Filipino Women Speak on Debt and Development (Philippine Study Tour) 1987-88 (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
    - Miscellaneous printed material 1984-88 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Center for Research on Women - Center for Self Help 1982-89 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Center for Women Policy Studies 1986-89 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Center for Women's Development - Centro de Salud Familair La Fe 1986-95, n, d. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Child Welfare League of America - City Wide Housing Coalition 1979-86,undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Children's Defense Fund 1982-90 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Church Women United - Coalition of Women of Color for Reproductive Health 1985-94, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Comite de Mujeres Puertorriquenas - Committee of 100 1984-95 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Women, Population, and the Environment - Cross Cultural Communication Center 1983-94, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Delta Sigma Theta - Democratic Socialists of America 1984-88, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - D. C. Commission for Women
    - Agendas, meeting minutes, correspondence and miscellaneous printed material 1984-89 (Box 12, Folder 8-9)
    - Annual reports 1980-87 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Case of A.C. 1987-88, [see also International Council of African Women] (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Challenge of Nairobi 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - "D.C. Commission for Women" (newsletter) 1987-88 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - "Women's Rights to Women Leaders: The D.C. Commission for Women, Highlights and Legislative History 1967-87," 1987 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission - For the Love of Children 1978-96 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Ford Foundation 1986 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Foundation for a Compassionate Society 1988-89 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Foundation for African American Women 1992-98 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Fund for Black Women - Fund for Southern Communities 1986-95, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Gabriela, [see also Center for Global Education - Filipino women Speak on Debt,Development and Democracy and SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES - Countries - Philippines]
    - Miscellaneous printed material 1988-91 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - "Women's Update" 1987-89 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Georgians For Choice - Grassroots International 1986,1991 undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Grassroots Unity conference undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Development Group for Alternative Policies - Health Policy Advisory Center 1973-86, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Hispanic Health Council 1987, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Ida B. Wells Collective - International Wages for Housework Campaign 1988-94, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - International Black Women's Congress - International Convention On The Elimination of Discrimination Against Women 1985-88, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - International Council of African Women
    - African Women Rising 1985-89 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - A. C. case 1988, [see also D.C. Commission for Women] (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence 1985-88, undated (Box 14, Folder 9-10)
    - History and organization information 1986-89, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Mailing lists undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Meetings 1986-88, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous 1985-88, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Conferences, events, programs 1984-89, undated SERIES IV. ORGANIZATION FILES (continued) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - International Council of Women - International League for the Rights and Liberation of the Peoples 1985-89 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - International Resource Network of Women of African Descent 1985 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - International Women's Health Coalition - Japanese American Citizen's League 1983-89, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Justice Campaign 1986, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Kitchen Table: Women of Color Press - League of United Latin American Citizens 1980-2002, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Lutheran World Ministries - M & Y Associates 1974-86 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Madre 1986-89 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Men Stopping Violence 1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Metro D.C. Coalition for Choice - Mexican-American Legal and Defense Fund 1989, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Mexican-American Women's National Association 1983-86, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Michigan Women's Commission - Moscow Center for Gender Studies 1983-93, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Ms. Foundation 1986-89 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Multicultural Alliance for Reproductive Freedom - National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL) 1990-94, undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - National Alliance Against Racism and Political Repression - National Anti-Klan Network 1981-86, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People 1987-88, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - National Association of Colored Women's Clubs 1979-81 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - National Association of Commissions for Women - National Black Coalition 1938-85 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - National Black Independent Political Party- National Black Federation of Charities 1984-87, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - National Black United Front 1987-88 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - National Black Women's Health Project
    - Organizational material
      - Annual meetings 1988-89 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Articles and clippings undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Bylaws undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence 1988-93 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Finance Committee 1988 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Logos,vision and mission statement, chants and music undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Notes 1993-94 undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Promotional material 1985-87, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Programs and events
      - AIDS, [see also SERIES VI. SUBJECT FILES]
        - Aids Education Program 1988-89 (Box 17, Folder 11)
        - Black Women and AIDS Think Tank 1989 (Box 17, Folder 12)
        - From Cries and Whispers To Action; Black Women and Aids 1988 (Box 17, Folder 13)
          - Conference report, follow up and related material 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence 1988-89 (Box 17, Folder 15)
          - Notes 1989, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
          - Participants and mailing lists 1988 (Box 18, Folder 2)
          - Miscellaneous undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Black and Female: What is the Reality?" 1988 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Black Women's Health Issues (1st National Conference) 1983 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Black Women's Health Issues (2nd National Conference) 1990 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Black Women's Health Agenda (7th National Conference) 1993 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Politics and Black Women's Health undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Racism: Unlearning Racism 1986-89 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Reproductive Rights
        - Between Ourselves: Reproductive Freedom in the Black Community, A Forum for Women of Color 1986 (Box 18, Folder 10)
        - "Black Women and Reproductive Freedom" 1989 (Box 18, Folder 11)
        - Empowerment, Health, Reproductive Rights: An Agenda for Women of All Colors 1990 (NY) (Box 18, Folder 12)
        - Miscellaneous 1979-89, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Self Help
        - National Self Help Chapter Development Program 1989 (Box 18, Folder 14)
        - Roll Call: Sisters Wave Your Hands!, Self-Helpers Task Force 1989 (Box 18, Folder 15)
        - Self help developers 1988, 1990, undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
        - "Self Help Booklet" 1985 (Box 18, Folder 17)
        - "Self Help Manual" undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
        - Miscellaneous 1989, undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - Sistereach undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Wellness
        - Black Women's Wellness Center 1988 (Box 19, Folder 1)
        - "Empowerment Through Wellness" 1989 (Box 19, Folder 2)
        - "Rituals of Wellness" undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous 1986-90 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Publications and films (Box 19)
      - "On Becoming A Woman: Mothers & Daughters Talking Together" 1987-88 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Prenatal Caring: Training Manual for Outreach Workers Liaison" 1990 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Vital Signs 1987-94 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Affiliates: District of Columbia, New York, Bay Area, Philadelphia 1986-89, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - National Black Women's Political Leadership Caucus undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - National Campaign to Restore Abortion Funding 1983-88 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - National Catholic Conference For Interracial Justice - National Caucus of Labor Committees 1985, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - National Center for Human Rights Education
    - Workshop/Presentation chronicles, "We Are Wonderful" Scrapbook 1996 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Workshop/Presentation chronicles, "We Are Wonderful" Scrapbook 1997 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Workshop/Presentation chronicles, Scrapbook 1998 (Box 20, Folder 1-5)
    - Workshop/Presentation chronicles, "We Are Wonderful" Scrapbook 1999 (Box 20, Folder 6-7)
    - Workshop/Presentation chronicles, "We Are Wonderful" Scrapbook 2000 (Box 21, Folder 1-3)
    - Workshop/Presentation chronicles, "We Are Wonderful" Scrapbook 2001 (Box 21, Folder 4-5)
    - Workshop/Presentation chronicles, "We Are Wonderful" Scrapbook 2003 (Box 21, Folder 6-7)
    - Untitled scrapbook 2000-2003 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
  - National Coalition Against Censorship - National Coalition of Black Voter Participation 1985-93 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - National Coalition of Black Lesbians and Gays 1984-88 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - National Coalition of 100 Black Women - National Conference of Black Lawyers 1982-91, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - National Council of Negro Women 1983-1991, undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - National Family Planning and Reproductive Health Association 1986-88, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - National Family Planning and Reproductive Health Association 1986-88, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force Policy Institute 1991 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - National Institute for Women of Color 1984-89, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - National Latina Health Organization- National Organization Responding to AIDS 1984-88, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - National Organization for Women
    - Affiliates 1979-89 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Articles and clippings 1979-93 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Conferences and events
      - It's a Man's World Unless Women Vote 1983 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - March for Women's Equality and Women's Lives 1989 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - March for Women's Lives 1988 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - National NOW Conference 1979 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Women of Courage, Healing Hatred (National Now Conference) 1994 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence 1984-95 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - History
      - Miscellaneous historical information 1966-71 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - 20th Anniversary, [see also SERIES VII. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS - Video tapes] (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - 25th Anniversary 1992 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Legal Defense and Education Fund 1986, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Mailing lists undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Minority Women's Committee 1971-82 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous 1983-89 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Subjects, [see also SERIES VI. SUBJECTS]
      - Affirmative action 1966-87 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Apartheid 1985-86, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Brenda Vaughan imprisonment 1988 (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Civil rights 1983, undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Consciousness raising undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Equal education for girls 1988 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Equal Rights Amendment 1981 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Family and Medical Leave Act 1987 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Health care reform 1994 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - Lesbian rights 1988 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - Minimum wage 1988 (Box 24, Folder 17)
      - Native Americans 1984-86 (Box 24, Folder 18)
      - Prostitution 1986 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Reproductive rights
        - Facts on Reproductive Rights, a Resource Manual 1989 (Box 25, Folder 2)
        - Abortion 1986-89 (Box 25, Folder 3)
        - Reproduction Rights Resource Kit 1983-87 (Box 25, Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous 1987 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Teen pregnancy 1985-86 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Sexual privacy 1986 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - United Nations 1974-79 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Women and insurance 1985 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Women and poverty undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Women and the media 1984 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Women of Color
        - Calendar of Events 1983-88 (Box 25, Folder 12)
        - Correspondence 1979-89 (Box 25, Folder 13)
        - Mailing lists and labels 1985-86 (Box 25, Folder 14)
        - Mailing lists and labels 1985-86 (Box 26, Folder 1-6)
        - Mailing lists and labels 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 1)
        - Miscellaneous 1981-83 (Box 27, Folder 2)
        - NOW March 1989 (Box 27, Folder 3)
        - Racism 1979-89 (Box 27, Folder 4)
        - Reproductive rights
          - Conferences, [see also SERIES VII. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS - Audiotapes]
            - Between Ourselves, Reproductive Freedom in the Black Community 1986 (Box 27, Folder 5-6)
            - Between Ourselves, Women of Color and Reproductive Rights 1987 (Box 27, Folder 7)
            - Between Ourselves, 1st National Conference- Brochure Request Forms 1987 (Box 28, Folder 1)
            - Between Ourselves, 1st National Conference 1987 (Box 28, Folder 2-6)
            - Between Ourselves, 1st National Conference 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1-3)
            - Reproductive Rights Forum for Women of Color 1986 (Box 29, Folder 4)
          - Resource list 1987 (Box 29, Folder 5)
          - Video 1988 (Box 29, Folder 6)
        - Title X Women of Color Coalition 1987-1988 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - National Pinochle Association 1991 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - National Political Congress of Black Women 1984-87 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - National Project on Ethnic America 1973 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - National Rainbow Coalition 1987-89, [see also SERIES V. CONFERENCES AND EVENTS - Democratic National Convention] (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - National Resource Center on Domestic Violence 1994, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - National Resource Center on Women and AIDS 1988 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - National Task Force on Prostitution 1986, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - National Urban League 1981-82 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - National Welfare rights Union - National Women's Conference Center 1987-90, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - National Women's Health Network
    - Organization
      - Board of directors
        - Meetings
          - June, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 10)
          - November, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 1)
          - March, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 2)
          - July, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 3)
          - October, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 4)
          - February, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 5)
          - June, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 6)
          - June,1991 (Box 32, Folder 1)
          - November, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 2)
        - Membership lists and nomination forms 1990, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
        - Miscellaneous correspondence and memoranda 1988-90, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence and notes 1988, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Executive Committee
        - August, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 6)
        - December, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Nominations and Elections 1990 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Personnel 1992, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Programs and events
      - Bright Ribbons Committee 1995 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Women and Health Meeting 1988 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Publications: Network News 1988-93 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Subjects, [see also SERIES VI. SUBJECTS]
      - Abortion 1988-2005, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - AIDS and Women (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Breast cancer 1988-89 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Contraception
        - Depo provera 1985-88, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
        - Intrauterine devices (Dalkon Shield) 1988-89, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
        - Norplant 1989 (Box 33, Folder 4)
        - Oral contraception 1988-89, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
        - Miscellaneous 1988 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Cosmetic surgery 1989 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Diethlstilbestrol (DES) 1981-89, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Female condom 1988-90, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Health care reform 1988-89 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Hormone replacement therapy 1988-90 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Mammograms 1989 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Maternal and child health 1988-90, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Nestle Boycott 1988 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Pharmaceutical dumping 1979 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Reproductive technologies 1986-87 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Toxic shock syndrome undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Weight loss 1988-89 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - National Women's Health Resource Center - National Women's Studies Association 1988-89 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Native American Community Health Board 1987-88 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Network of East-West Women 1990-93, undated (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Network of East-West Women 1990-93, undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - National Resource Center on Domestic Violence 1994, undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - New York Civil Liberties Union - Open Meadows Foundation 1975-92, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Organizacion Mexicana de Mujeres 1987-88 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Organization for Black Struggle 1987-89 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Organization of Chinese American Women 1983-86 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Organization of Pan Asian American Women 1983-89 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Pacific Institute for Women's Health - Radical Women 1985-97, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Ranos Institute 1992-93, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Rape Crisis Center 1980-93, undated, [see also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS AND PHOTOGRAPHS - Photographs] (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Religious Coalition for Abortion Rights
      - In Defense of Roe 1989 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - ==Publications (Box 35)
        - Options 1987-88 (Box 35, Folder 1)
        - Miscellaneous 1989, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Women of Color Partnership
        - Common Ground 1988-91 (Box 35, Folder 3)
        - Conferences: Between Ourselves, A Reproductive Rights Forum 1986-87 (Box 35, Folder 4-5)
        - Miscellaneous 1985-90 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous 1985-88 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Religious Response Network - Rural Southern Voice for Peace 1989-93, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Rutgers Reproductive Rights Project 1986-87 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Sandy Nelson Defense Committee - Sinew Juice Club 1987, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Sister City Project - Sisterhood in Support of Sisters in South Africa 1993-95, undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - SisterLove 1990-94 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - SisterSong undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Sister to Sister Project - Trans Africa 1984-91, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Trans Africa Forum 1985-88, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Ujamaa Shule - United Black Fund of Greater Washington D.C. 1985-89 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - United Nations, [see also SERIES V. CONFERENCES AND EVENTS]
      - Centre Against Apartheid 1984 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Development Fund for Women 1985-87, undated (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - U.N. Decade for Women 1984-85 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous 1987-88 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - United Neighborhood Centers of America - Western States Center 1983-94,undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Women Against Military Madness - Women and Minority Events Calendar 1986-94, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Women Hurt In Systems of Prostitution Engaged in Revolt (WHISPER) - Women of All Red Nations 1981-95, undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Women of Color Access Project 1987-88, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Women of Color Leadership Council - Women of Color Reproductive Health Forum 1991, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Women of Color Reproductive Rights Network 1988, undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Women of Color Task Force - Women's Center of Osaka 1984-91, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Women's Environment and Development Organization - Women's Equal Opportunity Council 1983-95, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Women's Fund of Greater Washington 1986-88, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Women's Global Network on Reproductive Rights
      - Newsletter 1985-93 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous 1985-97, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Women's Health Institute - World Development Forum 1987-94, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - YMCA - Zero Population Growth 1980-95, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)